*Your info
	-ID: 1412280
	-Name: Trần Hoàng Lâm
	-Email: malartsoft@gmail.com

*What you have done
	-Completed app paint and dll
	-Funtions
		+ Draw 3 types of objects: Line, Rectangle, Ellipse.
		+ Save file binary data equal interface dialog save file.
		+ Load file binary data equal interface dialog open file.
		+ Store & load all drawing functions in an external dll file.
		+ Clear screen 
		+ Change size screen

*Link youtube guide: https://youtu.be/yB7aeroyO1Q

*Link github: https://github.com/malartsoft/Expense

*Main flow
	
	1. Open app Paint
	2. Choose Line or Rectangle or Ellipse to draw
	3. Choose File => Save to open interface diaglog Save file, input name different with name
		existed, chosse button save to save
	4. Press button to clear screen
	5. Choose File => Open to open interface dialog Open file, choose file saved to open
	6. Choose File => Exit to exit program.

*Additional flow
	6.1 Choose button 'X' to exit
